Are you a middle-aged Italian man that
just moved out of his parents house?
I
bet you didn't, but let's say you did.
bet you're having a tough time getting
some sleep, aren't you?
Do you miss the
warm embrace of your overbearing mother?
How about the smell of her delicious cooking?
Or how about that low rumbling
you hear at night coming from her sleep
apnnea machine?
Well, we've got the
perfect solution for you.
Introducing My Mother,
the body pillow for Italian
American men.
Say goodbye to tossing and
turning and getting that grease all over
your pillows.
My Mother comes with a grease trap.
Boy, this thing stinks.
Every My mother pillow is customized to
feel exactly like your mother.
How do you respect a man that doesn't do
his own laundry?
You know why I do my
own laundry? You, ma.
The My mother pillow comes with snuggle detection.
Hello, Mrs. Delvecianagio.
So, if anybody else tries to sneak in
and give her a squeeze, she's going to
let out an alarm.
What the [ __ ] are you doing?
Oh, the disrespect.
I'm a boy, too, Tommy. I got needs.
Get the [ __ ]
You're probably thinking to yourself, a
product like this must cost around what?
Three fetuccini? No, we're going to
knock it down to one fetuccini.
And for
the price of a fetachccini and shrimp,
you can also get My Girl Pillow.
The My
Girl Pillow design is shaped exactly
like the girl you dated in high school
that ended up with that Jew doctor.
With
My Mother and My Girl Pillows, you can sleep easy
knowing they're both going to
be arguing over which one you love more
all night.
Ma, she's not like that. Will you stop?
Both pillows are made of a very strong fabric,
so you don't have to worry about
any of your buddies coming in and
cutting a [ __ ] hole in these things,
especially before you've had your
chance.
Ma, what are you doing?
O, I'm coming over here.
My mother, the body pillow for Italian-American men.
Good night, Ma.
Wow.
What are you talking about?
Oh, the Sopranos.